http://www.victorialaw.com/privacy-policy-terms-service/

Privacy Policy and Terms of Service - David Aujla - Immigration Lawyer Vancouver
Set Up A Consultation
Privacy Policy and Terms of ServiceHome » Privacy Policy and Terms of Service
Terms of Service
1. Terms
By accessing the web site at https://www.bcimmigration.com/, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
2. Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s web site;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by David Aujla Immigration Lawyer at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
3. Disclaimer
The materials on David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s web site are provided “as is”. David Aujla Immigration Lawyer makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, David Aujla Immigration Lawyer does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
4. Limitations
In no event shall David Aujla Immigration Lawyer or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s Internet site, even if David Aujla Immigration Lawyer or a David Aujla Immigration Lawyer authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
5. Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. David Aujla Immigration Lawyer does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. David Aujla Immigration Lawyer may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. David Aujla Immigration Lawyer does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
6. Links
David Aujla Immigration Lawyer has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by David Aujla Immigration Lawyer of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.
7. Site Terms of Use Modifications
David Aujla Immigration Lawyer may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
8. Governing Law
Any claim relating to David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s web site shall be governed by the laws of British Columbia without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us, and it is David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. David Aujla Immigration Lawyer may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at David Aujla Immigration Lawyer’s sole discretion.
An Associate of
About David AujlaDavid Aujla has advised clients world-wide for over 40 years and is a well-established Canadian Immigration lawyer with offices in both Vancouver and Victoria, British Columbia...
Read more
Vancouver OfficeDavid Aujla Immigration Lawyer247- 2628 Granville Street,
Vancouver, British Columbia Canada V6H 4B4604-630-2244
info@bcimmigration.comDirections
Victoria Office David Aujla Immigration Lawyer800 - 1070 Douglas Street,
Victoria, British Columbia Canada V8W 2C4250-383-3542
info@bcimmigration.comDirections
Social
All Rights Reserved © 2020 BCImmigration.com | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | Website by Iris
« Covid-19 Notice: Safety and support for our clients. Read more »
This site uses cookies. In order to continually improve this site, we remember and store information about how you use it.Accept & Continue
